

# Camilo Restrepo

# Front-end Developer



https://cv-camilo-restrepo.netlify.app



https://github.com/R4D4M4NTHYS24



camilorg2017@gmail.com

I am a Front-End developer and UX/UI designer with over 2 years of experience. I have worked on various projects ranging from designing and developing custom websites to maintaining and updating existing sites. My skill set includes modern front-end technologies such as React, Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, design skills with Figma, as well as working with agile methodologies such as Lean and Design Thinking. In addition, I have 14 years of experience in computer technical support. You can find me on LinkedIn as: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-camilo-restrepo-gomez-831272162">https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-camilo-restrepo-gomez-831272162</a>

# **Experience**

#### 2023 - Present

### **Crwn Clothing React Store**

Massive e-commerce application similar to Shopify using React, Redux, React Hooks, React Suspense, Context API, React Router, TypeScript, PWA, Styled-Components and Firebase.

https://crwn-clothing-react-cr.netlify.app

#### 2022 - 2023

#### **Fitness Tracker**

Fitness activity tracker developed using Angular 15, utilizing Angular Material 15, Angular Fire 7.5, and NgRx 15 libraries. (Try it using the following credentials: test@test.com, 1234567).

https://ng-fitness-tracker-efef9.web.app

#### 2020 - 2022

#### **Marvel-Initiative**

This web app was built by creating high-fidelity prototypes with Figma. It uses the official Marvel API through modern JavaScript.

https://marvel-initiative-5bf01.web.app

#### 2019 - 2020

#### **Omnifood**

Website built with semantic HTML5, modern CSS3, flexbox, and CSS Grid. https://omnifood-camilo.netlify.app

## **Education**

#### 2023

### **Zero To Mastery Academy**

I successfully completed the Complete React Developer course in 2023 (with Redux, Hooks, GraphQL) taught by Andrei Neagoie and Yihua Zhang at <u>Zero To Mastery</u>.

#### 2022

#### **Academind**

I successfully completed the Angular (Complete Application) course with Angular Material, Angularfire, and NgRx as taught by Maximilian Schwarzmüller at <u>Academind</u>.

### 2021

#### Udemy

- I successfully completed the UX Design: UX/UI User Experience + Figma course as taught by <u>Javier</u> <u>Cañas</u> at Udemy.
- I successfully completed the Complete JavaScript 2021 Course: From Zero to Expert! as taught by <u>Jonas Schmedtmann</u> at Udemy.
- I successfully completed the "Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS" course as taught by <u>Jonas</u> <u>Schmedtmann</u> at Udemy.